

mahdi shams

DoB: 1986-09-16

Marital Status: Married Military Service: Served

creative, curious and interested in new topic for learning .

I am familiar with and have worked with Python in various fields, like data science and web development.

In the field of data analysis, I am familiar with and have worked with the following libraries: seaborn, scikit-learn, Pandas, numpy.

Also in the field of web I have worked with Django framework that you can see my sample in bottom of pages.

Contact



shamsmahdi098@gmail.com



(+98)9124399441



02166051624

Toos avenue, Jeihoon Intersection, no.244, apartment3, Tehran, Iran

Education

Diploma of math

Institute/University: Emami al-agha Tehran, Iran GPA: 18/60 2000 - 2004

Branch: Systems technology Institute/University: west Tehran

Tehran, Iran GPA: 16 From 2018

Master of MBA

Work Experiences

expert

komiteh emdad

Tehran, Iran

February 2014 - June 2016

Tasks and Achievements:

■ create automation software with excel for maintenance

supervisor

fanava card

Tehran, Iran

June 2017 - June 2018

Tasks and Achievements:

■ create search software with access

manager

fanava card

Tehran, Iran

August 2019 - July 2020

expert

fanava card

Tehran, Iran

June 2016 - June 2017

Bachelor of electricity

Institute/University: south of tehran azad

Branch: power

Tehran, Iran GPA: 13/60 2004 - 2009

islamic university

Tasks and Achievements:

■ create search software with excel

boss

fanava card

Tehran, Iran

June 2018 - August 2019

Head of Inspection Office

sayan card

Tehran, Iran

From: July 2020

Skills



60 %



microsoft excell

programming language python

html 5







django webframwork

Languages

English

Reading Level

Writing Level

Listening Level

Speaking Level







javascript

jquery

Ajax

Certificates

english language

Institute: Faculty of Foreign Slaves, University of Tehran

November 2013

microsoft excel

Institute: Faculty of Engineering, University of Tehran

Anger management

Institute: Pardaz gostar tadbir

Principles of telephone conversation

Institute: Pardaz gostar tadbir

Customer satisfaction management standard ISO10002

Institute: behboud keifiat kimia

django framework

Institute: Tehran Technical Complex

microsoft sql server

Institute: Tehran Technical Complex

javascript

Institute: Tehran Technical Complex

jquery

Institute: Tehran Technical Complex

Ajax

Institute : Tehran Technical Complex

Projects

Professional weblog

January 1400

this weblog deployed by django framework (belongs to python) and has options like: search, tags, rssfeed, share blog by email and ...

Link: http://arrayarcstudio.ir/blog/

online shop

March 1400

this weblog deployed by django framework (belongs to python) and has options like: filter according to category, products, internet payment gateway , \dots

Link: https://arrayarcstudio.ir/